Little Fox
The tale of Jemima puddle duck.
Episode 2.
A new friend.
Jemima hiked up a big hill.
From the top, she saw a forest.
It was very far away.
Oh lay my eggs there.
She said.
Jemima ran and flapped her wings.
Up, up, up she went.
Jemima flew through the air.
Soon, she was flying over the forest.
She saw a nice spot and landed.
Jemima took a few steps and stopped.
A stranger sat on a tree stump.
He wore fancy clothes.
Jemima didn't know that he was a fox.
The fox looked up from his newspaper.
He smiled.
Hello.
Said the fox.
Are you lost?
What a nice gentleman.
Thought Jemima.
No, I'm not lost.
She said.
I need a place to lay my eggs.
The fox grinned.
I love eggs.
He said.
And I love little ducklings.
Oh?
Said Jemima.
Come with me, dear.
Said the fox.
His teeth sparkled in the sun.
You can lay your eggs in my shed.
It will be very safe there.